Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive 1989-2004 MSS 191
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Red Hot + Country, 1994
  Red Hot + Country was released in 1994 by Mercury Nashville, featuring classic country and rock songs performed by old and new country artists. The album received two Grammy nominations. An accompanying home video was released by PolyGram Video. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Close Up The Honky Tonks", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - "Fire And Rain", 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - "Forever Young", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - "Keep On The Sunnyside", 1994 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - "Pictures Don't Lie", 1994 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - "Teach Your Children", 1993 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - "Willie Short", 1994 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Active, [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Advances from PolyGram Records, Inc. (video label), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Bogguss, Suzy, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Brooks & Dunn, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Browne, Jackson, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Cash, Johnny, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Chestnutt, Mark, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Clairol cassette single + CD info, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Clearances - Labels, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Clearances - Publishing, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Contact list, [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Crowell, Rodney, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Disk, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
    - Eddy, Duane (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Gilmore, Jimmy Dale, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Griffith, Nanci, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Hoffman, Rand, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Kershaw, Sammy, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Liberty Records, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Licensing, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Licensing, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Licensing - Clairol cassette single, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Loveless, Patty, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Mattea, Kathy, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Nelson, Willie, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Ono Lennon, Yoko, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Other labels, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Painting waivers, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Parton, Dolly, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Perkins, Carl, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Recording budget and expenses, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Royalties audit - Contracts, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Royalty statement, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Ryman Auditorium event - Crew all access pass, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Ryman Auditorium event - VIP pass, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Sales breakdown, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - The Scruggs, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Signed contracts, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Signed synchronization licenses, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Stuart, Marty, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Sullivan, Jerry and Tammy, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - TV show, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Video synchronization rights, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Video tracking log, c.a. 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - VIDEO WAIVERS (Restricted), 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Watson, Doc, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Wilco, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Address re: ribbon controversy, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Clairol cassette single, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Clairol cassingles, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Decals - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Information packet master, c.a. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Media guidelines for participating artists, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pamphlets - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Press release, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville (Promotional), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Red ribbon badge - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Table tents - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photograph: Stuart, Marty, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Photographs: Recording artists, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Rodney Crowell, Waylon Jennings, Nanci Griffith, Kathy Mattea, Mark Collie, Radney Foster, John Hiatt, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Duane Eddy, Carl Perkins, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - mostly crew, John Carlin, Randy Scruggs (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, Levon Helm, Radney Foster, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Mark Collie, Earl Scruggs, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Sammy Kershaw, Kathy Mattea, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Earl Scruggs, Billy Ray Cyrus, Levon Helm, crew, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Jimmie Dale Gilmore, Radney Foster, crew, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Carl Perkins, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Duane Eddy, Carl Perkins, The Mavericks, Shelby Lynne, Billy Ray Cyrus, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - All, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Radney Foster, Levon Helm, Rodney Crowell, Nanci Griffith, crew, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Randy Scruggs, Billy Ray Cyrus (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, John Carlin, Jimmie Dale Gilmore, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, Jimmie Dale Gilmore, Radney Foster, Carl Perkins, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - John Carlin, crew, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium, most credited to Theresa Montgomery and Jed Dekalb, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Slides: Recording artists, [n.d.] (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville (tire packaging), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Red Hot + Country; PolyGram Video, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Red Hot + Country CD inserts (partial), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, 1994
  Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool was released by GRP Records in 1994, featuring collaborations between jazz performers and hip hop artists. A documentary film focusing on the impact of AIDS on communities of color was broadcast on PBS in tandem with the album release, and released on home video by PolyGram Video. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advances from ITVS and GRP Records (label), 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Advertising, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Approval memos, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Audio tracking log, 1994 - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Axium Productions, Inc. (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Bank account, 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Billing - Artwork (Restricted), 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Billing - Paid, 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Billing - Receipts (Restricted), 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Billing - Sent (not paid), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Budgets and information for independents, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Byrd, Donald / Guru (Restricted), 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Carter, Ron, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cherry, Don, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Coltrane, Alice, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Hot 97 FM, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Digable Planets (Restricted), 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Film production cost summary, [n.d.] (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Film production files (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Franti, Michael, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Groove Collective, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - GRP, [n.d.] (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Maxell 1.44 MB disk
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Incognito, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - ITVS (Independent Television Service, Inc.), 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - The Last Poets (Restricted), 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Live shoot releases (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Marsalis, Branford, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - MC Solaar / Rakhim, 1994 - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Music videos (Restricted), 1991 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - NdegeOcello, Me'shell (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - The Pharcyde, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Publishing waivers - all tracks, 1993 - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - RHO#6 Stolen Moments, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - The Roots (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Rosenworld, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Royalties audit, 1996 - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Royalty statement, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Sales breakdown for foreign royalties, 1996 - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - TV agreements (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - TV releases (Restricted), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Us3, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Video folder, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Video tracking log, c.a. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Watson, Wah Wah, 1994 - 1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Watts Prophets, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Condoms - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Flier - Live at the Supper Club, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Fliers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool home video, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Fliers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool track listing, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Information packet, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Invitation to advance screening of Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Invitations to live filmed event at Supper Club, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Mugs - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, [n.d.] (Box 36)
      General note
      Mugs are housed in a separate box - Box 36.
    - Postcard ad - "You better stop and think about it", [1994] (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Postcard ads - "Time is moving on, you better get with it before it's gone.", [1994] (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Cool, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Postcard invitations to "A Celebration of Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool", c.a. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Promotional single: "Proceed II," The Roots w/ Roy Ayers; GRP Records, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Red Hot On Impulse!; GRP Records (Promotional), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Red Hot Organization Presents: Live at the Supper Club, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sample: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool (Japanese version); GRP Records, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Stickers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    All photographs are black and white.
    - Contact sheets: Credited to Kristine Larsen, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Film negative fragments (16 mm): Beard, skyline + brick wall, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Film negatives and photo: SM Party (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Mock-ups: Donald Byrd; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay & MC Solaar; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay, MC Solaar & GURU; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay, Ron Carter & MC Solaar; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Mock-up: Lester Bowie & The Digable Planets; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Mock-up: Me'Shell NgedeOcello; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Mock-up: Wah Wah Watson; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Photographs: Beard, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Photograph: Hancock, Herbie, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Photographs: Marsalis, Branford; credited to Bruce Caines, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Photographs: Publicity stills of artistes (Box 38)
    - Preservation negatives: Skyline + beard, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Slides: Mostly for Red Hot on Impulse, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Slides: Mostly publicity stills, one credited to Guy Aroch, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Slides (color): Publicity stills of artistes, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Slides: Publicity stills of artistes (titled "More b+w copies" but contents are not all black and white) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - A Little on the CD Side: Musician Magazine's New Music Sampler, Volume 16; Ivy Hill, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool; GRP Records, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool; PolyGram Video, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool VHS sleeve, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Subseries E: Awards
    - Golden Gate Award, San Francisco International Film Festival, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Silver Apple Award, National Educational Media Network, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, 1995
  Red Hot + Bothered was initially released in 1995 as "Red Hot + Bothered Volume I Number 1" and "Red Hot + Bothered Volume I Number 1," two 10” EP's with limited edition fanzines by indie writers and artists. A full-length CD was later released in the same year, containing extra tracks not available on the vinyl EP's. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advance against profits from Warner Bros. Records, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Babe the Blue Ox - "Hazmats" video, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Budget/billing, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Clearances - Signed, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Invoices - Paid, 1994 - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Invoices - Pending, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Legal information, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Marketing, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Project accounting for "Fanzine", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Publishing rights, 1994 - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - RH+Bothered #2 archive, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Flier - Red Hot + Bothered 1, [1995] (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Bothered 2, [1995] (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Invitation to release of Red Hot + Bothered, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Press releases, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Stickers - Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Table tent - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Slides (color): Red Hot & Bothered #2 zine cover, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Bothered; Kinetic Records, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Red Hot + Bothered CD insert (back), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
  This series encompasses both "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM/Video and "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" enhanced audio CD.
  Released by WAX TRAX / TVT in 1996, "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" was an offshoot of The Beat Experience, a project exploring the legacy of the Beat generation produced by The Red Hot Organization in association with the Whitney Museum of American Art. "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM combines text, jazz, underground films and visual art to anthologize the period, while "The Beat Experience" video is an hour TV show that presents the era in a contemporary edit of archive filmclips, sound bites, music and abstract imagery.
  (Reference: Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening flier; http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Adamson, Barry, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Advances from Wax Trax Records (label) and Voyager (distributor), 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Baraka, Amiri / DJ Spooky (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Beat Disk (contents: Budget.xls, Footage.xls, flmcred.doc & VHS list), [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 5)
      TDK micro floppy disk
    - Billing: Mastering, Editing, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget notes, [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budget / Paid invoices (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Carney, Ray, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Clearances, 1995 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Clearances: Labels, Artists, Publish, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Contracts, CD-ROM & Film: Outstanding, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Credits, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Distribution, 1995 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - DJ Krush, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Broadcast Network, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Expenses: Party/Event, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Footage (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Footage, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Laika / My Bloody Valentine, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - McBride, Christian / DJ Krazy, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Masters, 1995 - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Meat Beat Manifesto, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Music - Masters, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Music - Publishers, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Music / Spoken word, [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Ndegocello, Me'Shell, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Notes, "John's", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Notes, Lisa [Hacken]'s (Research coordinator), 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Offbeat Archive, [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Paid Invoices (Restricted), 1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Pending / Money received, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Publishing, 1995 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Red Hot and Beat, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Royalty statement, 1996 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Shapero, Alyson (Marketing consultant) (Restricted), 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Skylab, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stills, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Includes listing of images to appear on CD-ROM and photocopies of two Dennis Hopper images. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said images.
    - Stills, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Includes photocopies of 11 images featuring Kerouac, Ginsberg, Burroughs and more. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for images appearing on CD-ROM.
    - Synchronization licenses, 1995 - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Text, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Includes text and images to appear on CD-ROM. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said text and images.
    - Text, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - TVT Records, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Video tracking log, 1995 - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Voyager Company, 1996 - 1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Wax Trax Records / TVT Records (label), 1995 - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Fliers for "Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening" and "The Beat Experience" (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Mousepads labeled "BEATPAD" featuring Sue Coe drawing, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Postcard invitations to exhibition of work by Gary Panter and David Sandlin "to celebrate the release of THE BEAT EXPERIENCE CD-ROM/VIDEO and OFFBEAT ENHANCED AUDIO CD", c.a. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, compilation of 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Press release, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Promotional: The Beat Experience, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Stickers, [n.d.] (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Negatives: Sue Coe artwork, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Slides (black and white): Mostly portraits of artistes (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Slides (color): Offbeat and The Beat Experience covers (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - The Beat Experience, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Compact disc read-only memory
    - The Beat Experience, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Offbeat: A Red Hot Sound Trip, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Enhanced audio compact disc
- Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly
  America Is Dying Slowly was released in 1996 by Eastwest Records America. It features hip hop producers and rappers who had not previously worked together. (Reference: http://redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - 8Ball & MJG, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - America@ (RHO#7), 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Biz Markie, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Brian, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Buckwild, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cashflow/budget, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Common Sense, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Contact info, [n.d.] (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Contract copies, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Coolio (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - De La Soul (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Development budget, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Diamond D (Restricted), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Domino, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Elektra, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Recording sessions, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Famous Artists Agency, Inc.: Checks from De La Soul/Fishbone/Goodie Mob tour, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Fat Joe, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Financial statements, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Jungle Brothers, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Kool G Rap, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Label contracts, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - The Lost Boyz, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mac Mall (Restricted), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Masta Ace (Restricted), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - MC Lyte (Restricted), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mobb Deep (Restricted), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Money Boss Players (Restricted), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - O.C., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Organized Konfusion (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Paid bills, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Panasonic TV commercial, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Prince Paul, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Producer contracts, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Publishing, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot # 18, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Return to Helene Silverman / Final "America is Dying Slowly" Artwork, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Royalties: "I Breaks 'Em Off" / "The Hustle", 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - RZA, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Samples, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Session reports (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Skadanks, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Special Ed, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Spice 1, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 43)